.NET Migrate Command

Usage: dotnet migrate [options] <PROJECT_JSON/GLOBAL_JSON/SOLUTION_FILE/PROJECT_DIR>

Arguments:
  <PROJECT_JSON/GLOBAL_JSON/SOLUTION_FILE/PROJECT_DIR>   The path to one of the following:
                                                         - a project.json file to migrate.
                                                         - a global.json file, it will migrate the folders specified in global.json.
                                                         - a solution.sln file, it will migrate the projects referenced in the solution.
                                                         - a directory to migrate, it will recursively search for project.json files to migrate.
                                                         Defaults to current directory if nothing is specified.

Options:
  -h, --help                      Show help information
  -t, --template-file             Base MSBuild template to use for migrated app. The default is the project included in dotnet new.
  -v, --sdk-package-version       The version of the SDK package that will be referenced in the migrated app. The default is the version of the SDK in dotnet new.
  -x, --xproj-file                The path to the xproj file to use. Required when there is more than one xproj in a project directory.
  -s, --skip-project-references   Skip migrating project references. By default, project references are migrated recursively.
  -r, --report-file               Output migration report to the given file in addition to the console.
  --format-report-file-json       Output migration report file as json rather than user messages.
  --skip-backup                   Skip moving project.json, global.json, and *.xproj to a `backup` directory after successful migration.

