Template Instantiation Commands for .NET Core CLI

Usage: dotnet new [arguments] [options]

Arguments:
  template  The template to instantiate.

Options:
  -l|--list         Lists templates containing the specified name. If no name is specified, lists all templates.
  -lang|--language  Specifies the language of the template to create.
  -n|--name         The name for the output being created. If no name is specified, the name of the current directory is used.
  -o|--output       Location to place the generated output.
  -h|--help         Displays help for this command.
  --type            Shows a subset of the available templates. Valid values are "project", "item" or "other".
  --force           Forces content to be generated even if it would change existing files.
  --allow-scripts   Specify if post action scripts should run.


ASP.NET Core Web App (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Options:                                                              
  -au|--auth           The type of authentication to use              
                           None          - No authentication          
                           Individual    - Individual authentication  
                       Default: None                                  

  -uld|--use-local-db  Whether or not to use LocalDB instead of SQLite
                       bool - Optional                                
                       Default: false                                 


