

Usage:  [options]

Options:
  -l|--list         Lists templates containing the specified name. If no name is specified, lists all templates.
  -lang|--language  Specifies the language of the template to create.
  -n|--name         The name for the output being created. If no name is specified, the name of the current directory is used.
  -o|--output       Location to place the generated output.
  -h|--help         Displays help for this command.
  --type            Shows a subset of the available templates. Valid values are "project", "item" or "other".
  --force           Forces content to be generated even if it would change existing files.


ASP.NET Core Web API (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Options:                                                                             
  -f|--framework  The target framework for the project.                              
                      netcoreapp1.0    - Target netcoreapp1.0                        
                      netcoreapp1.1    - Target netcoreapp1.1                        
                  Default: netcoreapp1.1                                             

  --skip-restore  If specified, skips the automatic restore of the project on create.
                  bool - Optional                                                    
                  Default: false                                                     


ASP.NET Core Web API (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Options:                                                                             
  -f|--framework  The target framework for the project.                              
                      netcoreapp2.0    - Target netcoreapp2.0                        
                  Default: netcoreapp2.0                                             

  --skip-restore  If specified, skips the automatic restore of the project on create.
                  bool - Optional                                                    
                  Default: false                                                     


