.NET Publisher

Usage: dotnet publish [options]

Options:
  -h, --help                            Show help information
  -f, --framework <FRAMEWORK>           Target framework to publish for. The target framework has to be specified in the project file.
  -r, --runtime <RUNTIME_IDENTIFIER>    Publish the project for a given runtime. This is used when creating self-contained deployment. Default is to publish a framework-dependent app.
  -o, --output <OUTPUT_DIR>             Output directory in which to place the published artifacts.
  -c, --configuration <CONFIGURATION>   Configuration to use for building the project.  Default for most projects is  "Debug".
  --version-suffix <VERSION_SUFFIX>     Defines the value for the $(VersionSuffix) property in the project.
  --filter <profile.xml>                The XML file that contains the list of packages to be excluded from publish step.
  -v, --verbosity                       Set the verbosity level of the command. Allowed values are q[uiet], m[inimal], n[ormal], d[etailed], and diag[nostic]

