.NET Core NuGet Package Packer

Usage: dotnet pack [options]

Options:
  -h, --help                            Show help information
  -o, --output <OUTPUT_DIR>             Directory in which to place built packages.
  --no-build                            Skip building the project prior to packing. By default, the project will be built.
  --include-symbols                     Include packages with symbols in addition to regular packages in output directory.
  --include-source                      Include PDBs and source files. Source files go into the src folder in the resulting nuget package
  -c, --configuration <CONFIGURATION>   Configuration to use for building the project.  Default for most projects is  "Debug".
  --version-suffix <VERSION_SUFFIX>     Defines the value for the $(VersionSuffix) property in the project.
  -s, --serviceable                     Set the serviceable flag in the package. For more information, please see https://aka.ms/nupkgservicing.
  -v, --verbosity                       Set the verbosity level of the command. Allowed values are q[uiet], m[inimal], n[ormal], d[etailed], and diag[nostic]

